ANDREAN

IT SUPPORT

CONTACT

- 0899 8023 703
- Villa tomang baru Blok AB no.3A, Kutabumi, Kab. Tangerang 15560

EDUCATION

SMK Bonavita

2017 - 2020 Technical computers and networking

Buddhi Dharma University

2020-2024 Informatics Engineering

SKILLS

- Computer Troubleshooting
- Computer Networking
- Microsoft Office
- Scores 237 points for EPT EnglishScore by UBD (July 2024)
- Adobe Photoshop
- Computer Hardware and Software

PROFILE

A Bachelor's Degree graduate in Informatics Engineering, specializing in network specialists, with approximately 1 year of experience in IT Support. Skilled in technical aspects such as troubleshooting, installation, and configuration of both hardware and software. Experienced in providing IT technical support to users.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT SUPPORT

PT Shinseong Delta Tech Indonesia, Tangerang July 2022 - December 2022

- Provide technical support to users, including troubleshooting, installation, and configuration of hardware and software.
- Respond to user inquiries regarding computer and software usage.
- Assisted users in resolving issues with computers and software.
- Performed installation and configuration of hardware and software
- Troubleshoot technical issues.

INTERNSHIPS

WHL (WAREHOUSE LOCAL)

PT. Mitsuba Indonesia

Maret 2019 - Mei 2019

- Received goods from suppliers.
- Stored goods securely.
- Delivered goods to customers.

PORTOFOLIO/PROJECT

DESIGNING AND BUILDING A CCTV SECURITY MONITORING SYSTEM BASED ON IOT USING ARDUINO MICROCONTROLLER (Final Project, Buddhi Dharma University)

March 2024 - July 2024

This research discusses the design and development of a CCTV security monitoring system based on an Arduino microcontroller.

This system is developed using a PIR (Passive Infrared) sensor that can detect movement in front of the CCTV. When movement is detected, the CCTV captures and photographs the movement and sends a photo and warning text message through a Telegram bot to users and security staff.

The data captured by the CCTV will be stored in an SD card module as evidence.

Tools & Technologies: IoT, C (Language Programming), Arduino Board, Arduino IDE, ESP8266, PIR (Movement sensor), OV7670 (Camera Module), BOT Telegram, Telegram.

Link: https://doi.org/10.36040/jati.v8i6.11740